Guide to the International Association for Cultural Freedom Records 1941-1978
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Correspondence and Subject Files
  - Subseries I: Correspondence and Subject Files, 1948-1967
    - Sub-subseries 4: "D"
      - General Correspondence "D," 1960 (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence "D," 1961 (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence "D," 1962 (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence "D," 1963-1964 (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence "D," 1965 (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - Da Costa, Eric, 1954-1957 (Box 122, Folder 7)
      - Daedalus, 1963 (Box 122, Folder 8)
      - Daedalus, 1964 (Box 122, Folder 9)
      - Daedalus, 1965 (Box 122, Folder 10)
      - Daedalus, 1966 (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - Daniélou, Alain, 1956-1957 (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - d'Arschot, Ruby, "A-Q," 1960-1961 (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - d'Arschot, Ruby, "R-Z," 1960-1961 (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - d'Arschot, Ruby, 1963 (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - d'Arschot, Ruby, 1963 (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - Datta, Amlan- Datta, Sudhin, 1956-1961 (Box 123, Folder 7)
      - Daya, Drishan- Deakin, William, 1956-1959 (Box 123, Folder 8)
      - Degras, Jane, 1958-1959 (Box 123, Folder 9)
      - Denmark- Buhl, Jena, 1951-1953 (Box 123, Folder 10)
      - Denmark- Buhl, Jena, 1954-1955 (Box 123, Folder 11)
      - Denmark- Buhl, Jena, 1956-1957 (Box 123, Folder 12)
      - Denmark- Buhl, Jena, 1958 (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - Denmark- Fonsmark, Henning, 1958-1961 (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - Denmark- Jacobsen, Frode, 1958 (Box 124, Folder 3)
      - Denmark- Jacobsen, Frode, 1959-1966 (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - Denmark- Jacobsen, Frode, 1959 (Box 124, Folder 5)
      - Denmark- Jacobsen, Frode, 1960-1961 (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - Denmark- Derv, Tibor, 1959-1960 (Box 124, Folder 7)
      - Denmark- Dhingra, Baldoon, 1959-1960 (Box 124, Folder 8)
      - Denmark- Dhingra, Baldoon, "A-F," 1960 (Box 124, Folder 9)
      - Denmark- Dhingra, Baldoon, "G-P," 1960 (Box 124, Folder 10)
      - Denmark- Dhingra, Baldoon, "Q-Z," 1960 (Box 124, Folder 11)
      - Denmark- Dhingra, Baldoon, "A-O," 1960-1961 (Box 124, Folder 12)
      - Denmark- Dhingra, Baldoon, "D-Z," 1960-1961 (Box 124, Folder 13)
      - Denmark- Dhingra, Baldoon Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - Denmark- Dhingra, Baldoon Miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - Denmark- Dhingra, Baldoon Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - Denmark- Dhingra, Baldoon Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - Diamat, 1951 (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - Diamat Manuscripts, 1948 (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - Dolberg, Alexander, 1959-1962 (Box 125, Folder 7)
      - Draper, Theodore, 1962 (Box 125, Folder 8)
      - Draper, Theodore, 1963-1966 (Box 125, Folder 9)
      - Draper, Theodore, 1965 (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - Draper, Theodore, 1965-1967 (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - Duerdon, Dennis, 1961-1962 (Box 126, Folder 3)
      - Duerdon, Dennis, 1962 (Box 126, Folder 4)
      - Duerdon, Dennis, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 5)
      - Duerdon, Dennis, 1964 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Sub-subseries 5: "E"
      - General Correspondence "E," 1951-1956 (Box 126, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence "E," 1957-1959 (Box 127, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence "E," 1960-1963 (Box 127, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence "E," 1964-1966 (Box 127, Folder 3)
      - Egypt, 1954-1961 (Box 127, Folder 4)
      - Egypt, 1959-1960 (Box 127, Folder 5)
      - Egypt, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 6)
      - Egypt, 1962 (Box 127, Folder 7)
      - Egypt, 1962-1965 (Box 127, Folder 8)
      - Egypt, 1963-1966 (Box 127, Folder 9)
      - Egypt, undated (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - El Kholy, Abdo, 1960-1961 (Box 127, Folder 11)
      - El Kholy, Abdo, 1962-1963 (Box 128, Folder 1)
      - El Shoush, 1961-1965 (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - Emmanuel, Pierre, 1959-1962 (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - Emmanuel, Pierre, "A-C," 1960-1961 (Box 128, Folder 4)
      - Emmanuel, Pierre, "D-L," 1960-1961 (Box 128, Folder 5)
      - Emmanuel, Pierre, "M-Z," 1960-1961 (Box 128, Folder 6)
      - Emmanuel, Pierre, "The Role of the Congress," 1964 (Box 128, Folder 6a)
      - Emmanuel, Pierre, Suspended Spanish professors, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - Emmanuel, Pierre, Suspended Spanish professors, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 8)
      - Emmanuel, Pierre, Suspended Spanish professors, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 9)
      - Emmanuel, Pierre, Suspended Spanish professors, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 10)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1951 (Box 129, Folder 1)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1952 (Box 129, Folder 2)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1952 (Box 129, Folder 3)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1952 (Box 129, Folder 4)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1952 (Box 129, Folder 5)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1953 (Box 129, Folder 6)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1953 (Box 129, Folder 7)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1954 (Box 129, Folder 8)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1954 (Box 129, Folder 9)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1954 (Box 130, Folder 1)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1954 (Box 130, Folder 2)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1955 (Box 130, Folder 3)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1955 (Box 130, Folder 4)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1956 (Box 130, Folder 5)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1956 (Box 130, Folder 6)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1956 (Box 130, Folder 7)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1956 (Box 130, Folder 8)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1956 (Box 130, Folder 9)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1957 (Box 130, Folder 10)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1957 (Box 131, Folder 1)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1958 (Box 131, Folder 2)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1958 (Box 131, Folder 3)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1958 (Box 131, Folder 4)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1959 (Box 131, Folder 5)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1959 (Box 131, Folder 6)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1959 (Box 131, Folder 7)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1959 (Box 131, Folder 8)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1959 (Box 131, Folder 9)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1960 (Box 131, Folder 10)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1961 (Box 131, Folder 11)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1961 (Box 132, Folder 1)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1961 Folder 3: Encounter Correspondence, 1962 (Box 132, Folder 2)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 4)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1964 (Box 132, Folder 5)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1965 (Box 132, Folder 6)
      - Encounter Correspondence, 1966 (Box 132, Folder 7)
      - Encounter, Hall, John, 1956 (Box 132, Folder 8)
      - Encounter, Hall, John, 1960 (Box 132, Folder 9)
      - Encounter, Lasley, Melvin, 1960 (Box 132, Folder 10)
      - Encounter, Lasley, Melvin, 1961-1962 (Box 132, Folder 11)
      - Encounter, Lasley, Melvin, 1963-1964 (Box 133, Folder 1)
      - Encounter, Walmsley, Margot, 1956 (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - Encounter, British Society for Cultural Freedom, 1952 (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - Encounter, British Society for Cultural Freedom, 1952 (Box 133, Folder 4)
      - d'Epinay, René Lahve, 1950-1951 (Box 133, Folder 5)
      - Europa Features, 1951-1952 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Sub-subseries 6: "F"
      - General Correspondence "F," 1951-1954 (Box 133, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence "F," 1955-1956 (Box 133, Folder 8)
      - General Correspondence "F," 1957 (Box 133, Folder 9)
      - General Correspondence "F," 1958 (Box 133, Folder 10)
      - General Correspondence "F," 1959-1960 (Box 133, Folder 11)
      - General Correspondence "F," 1961 (Box 133, Folder 12)
      - General Correspondence "F," 1962 (Box 133, Folder 13)
      - General Correspondence "F," 1963-1964 (Box 134, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence "F," 1965-1966 (Box 134, Folder 2)
      - Farfield Foundation, 1953 (Box 134, Folder 3)
      - Farfield Foundation, 1954 (Box 134, Folder 4)
      - Farfield Foundation, 1955 (Box 134, Folder 5)
      - Farfield Foundation, 1956 (Box 134, Folder 6)
      - Farrell, James, 1955 (Box 134, Folder 7)
      - Farrell, James, 1956 (Box 134, Folder 8)
      - Farrell, James, 1957-1958 (Box 134, Folder 9)
      - Felin, Maria, 1952 (Box 134, Folder 10)
      - Fejto, François, 1958-1963 (Box 134, Folder 11)
      - Fejto, François manuscripts, 1957 (Box 134, Folder 12)
      - Fellowships and scholarships, 1965-1966 (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - Finland, 1960-1965 (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - Fleischman, Julius, 1952 (Box 135, Folder 3)
      - Fleischman, Julius, 1953-1954 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - Fleischman, Julius, 1954-1955 (Box 135, Folder 5)
      - Fleischman, Julius, 1956 (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - Fleischman, Julius, 1957 (Box 135, Folder 7)
      - Fleischman, Julius, 1958-1960 (Box 135, Folder 8)
      - Fleischman, Julius, 1961-1964 (Box 135, Folder 9)
      - Foote, Timothy, "A-C," 1964-1965 (Box 135, Folder 10)
      - Foote, Timothy, "D-F," 1964-1965 (Box 135, Folder 11)
      - Foote, Timothy, "G-H," 1964-1965 (Box 135, Folder 12)
      - Foote, Timothy, "I-L," 1964-1965 (Box 136, Folder 1)
      - Foote, Timothy, "M-P," 1964-1965 (Box 136, Folder 2)
      - Foote, Timothy, "Q-S," 1964-1965 (Box 136, Folder 3)
      - Foote, Timothy, "T-Z," 1964-1965 (Box 136, Folder 4)
      - Ford Foundation, Budget, 1962-1963 (Box 136, Folder 5)
      - Ford Foundation, Fellowships, 1957-1964 (Box 136, Folder 6)
      - Ford Foundation, Fellowships, 1957-1964 (Box 136, Folder 7)
      - Ford Foundation, International Affairs Program, 1953-1954 (Box 136, Folder 8)
      - Ford Foundation, International Affairs Program, 1955-1956 (Box 136, Folder 9)
      - Ford Foundation, International Affairs Program, 1957 (Box 136, Folder 10)
      - Ford Foundation, International Affairs Program, 1957 (Box 136, Folder 11)
      - Ford Foundation, International Affairs Program, 1959-1962 (Box 137, Folder 1)
      - Ford Foundation, International Affairs Program, W. A. Nielson and Michael Polyani 1957-1961 (Box 137, Folder 2)
      - Ford Foundation, Kerala State Research Project, 1958 (Box 137, Folder 3)
      - Ford Foundation, Miscellaneous, 1961-1963 (Box 137, Folder 4)
      - Ford Foundation, Miscellaneous, 1961-1963 (Box 137, Folder 5)
      - Ford Foundation, Miscellaneous, 1961-1963 (Box 137, Folder 6)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee, 1957 (Box 137, Folder 7)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee, 1958 (Box 137, Folder 8)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee, 1959 (Box 137, Folder 9)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 137, Folder 10)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 137, Folder 11)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee reports, 1957-1958 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee reports, 1957-1958 (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee reports, 1958-1959 (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee reports, 1958-1959 (Box 138, Folder 4)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee reports, 1960 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee reports, 1961 (Box 138, Folder 6)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee reports, 1962 (Box 138, Folder 7)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee reports, 1963 (Box 138, Folder 8)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee reports, 1964 (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - Ford Foundation, C.C.F. Planning Committee reports, 1965 (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - Forum- Torberg, Friedrich, 1952-1954 (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - Forum- Torberg, Friedrich, 1952-1954 (Box 139, Folder 4)
      - Forum- Torberg, Friedrich, 1955 (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - Forum- Torberg, Friedrich, 1956 (Box 139, Folder 6)
      - Forum- Torberg, Friedrich, 1956 (Box 139, Folder 7)
      - Forum- Torberg, Friedrich, 1957 (Box 139, Folder 8)
      - Forum- Torberg, Friedrich, 1958 (Box 139, Folder 9)
      - Forum- Torberg, Friedrich, 1959 (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Forum- Torberg, Friedrich, 1959 (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - Forum- Torberg, Friedrich, 1960 (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - Forum- Forum Kulturhilfe, 1957 (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - Forum- Forum Kulturhilfe, 1957 (Box 140, Folder 5)
      - Forum- Forum Kulturhilfe, 1957 (Box 140, Folder 6)
      - Forum- Forum Service, 1957-1959 (Box 140, Folder 7)
      - Forum- Forum World Features, 1965 (Box 140, Folder 8)
      - Forum- Forum World Features, 1966 (Box 140, Folder 9)
      - Foundations, 1964-1967 (Box 140, Folder 10)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Correspondence, "A-H," 1959-1964 (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Correspondence, "I-U," 1959-1964 (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Correspondence, "V-Z," 1959-1964 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Sub-subseries 7: "G"
      - General Correspondence "G," 1950-1951 (Box 141, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence "G," 1952-1954 (Box 141, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence "G," 1955-1956 (Box 141, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence "G," 1957 (Box 141, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence "G," 1957 (Box 141, Folder 8)
      - General Correspondence "G," 1958 (Box 141, Folder 9)
      - General Correspondence "G," 1959 (Box 141, Folder 10)
      - General Correspondence "G," 1960 (Box 141, Folder 11)
      - General Correspondence "G," 1961 (Box 142, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence "G," 1962 (Box 142, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence "G," 1963 (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence "G," 1964 (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence "G," 1965-1966 (Box 142, Folder 5)
      - Gadji, D. R., 1957 (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1954-1966 (Box 142, Folder 7)
      - Gandhi, Indira, 1955 (Box 142, Folder 8)
      - Gaspard, Armand, 1962-1966 (Box 142, Folder 9)
      - Germain, Andrés, 1958-1963 (Box 142, Folder 10)
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 142, Folder 11)
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 142, Folder 12)
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 142, Folder 13)
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 143, Folder 1)
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 143, Folder 2)
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 143, Folder 3)
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 143, Folder 4)
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 143, Folder 5)
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 143, Folder 6)
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 143, Folder 7)
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 143, Folder 8)
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 143, Folder 9)
      - Germany, 1952 (Box 143, Folder 10)
      - Germany, 1952 (Box 144, Folder 1)
      - Germany, 1953 (Box 144, Folder 2)
      - Germany, 1953-1959 (Box 144, Folder 2a)
      - Germany, 1954 (Box 144, Folder 3)
      - Germany, 1954 (Box 144, Folder 4)
      - Germany, 1955 (Box 144, Folder 5)
      - Germany, 1955 (Box 144, Folder 6)
      - Germany, 1956 (Box 144, Folder 7)
      - Germany, 1957 (Box 144, Folder 8)
      - Germany, 1958 (Box 144, Folder 9)
      - Germany, 1959 (Box 145, Folder 1)
      - Germany "A-K," 1960 (Box 145, Folder 2)
      - Germany "L-Z," 1960 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - Germany, "A-K," 1961 (Box 145, Folder 4)
      - Germany, "L-Z," 1961 (Box 145, Folder 5)
      - Germany, 1962-1963 (Box 145, Folder 6)
      - Germany, 1964-1965 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - Germany, 1966 (Box 145, Folder 8)
      - Germany, Berlin Bureau Manuscripts, 1951-1952 (Box 145, Folder 9)
      - Germany, Berlin Bureau Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 145, Folder 10)
      - Germany, Berlin Wall Project, 1961 (Box 145, Folder 11)
      - Germany, Birkenfeld, Gunther, 1952 (Box 145, Folder 12)
      - Germany, Birkenfeld, Gunther, 1952 (Box 146, Folder 1)
      - Germany, Birkenfeld, Gunther, 1952 (Box 146, Folder 2)
      - Germany, Birkenfeld, Gunther, 1952 (Box 146, Folder 3)
      - Germany, Birkenfeld, Gunther, 1953 (Box 146, Folder 4)
      - Germany, Birkenfeld, Gunther, 1953 (Box 146, Folder 5)
      - Germany, Birkenfeld, Gunther, 1953 (Box 146, Folder 6)
      - Germany, Birkenfeld, Gunther, 1953 (Box 146, Folder 7)
      - Germany, Birkenfeld, Gunther, 1954 (Box 146, Folder 8)
      - Germany, Cologne Bureau, 1959 (Box 146, Folder 9)
      - Germany, Cologne Bureau, 1960 (Box 146, Folder 10)
      - Germany, Cologne Bureau, 1961 (Box 147, Folder 1)
      - Germany, Cologne Bureau, 1962-1964 (Box 147, Folder 2)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1953 (Box 147, Folder 3)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1954 (Box 147, Folder 4)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1954 (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1954 (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1955 (Box 147, Folder 7)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1955 (Box 147, Folder 8)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1956 (Box 147, Folder 9)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1957 (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1958 (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1959 (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1960 (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1961 (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1962 (Box 148, Folder 6)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1963-1964 (Box 148, Folder 7)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1965 (Box 148, Folder 8)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau, 1966 (Box 148, Folder 9)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau Clippings and Announcements, 1964-1966 (Box 148, Folder 10)
      - Germany, Hamburg Bureau Clippings and Announcements, 1964-1966 (Box 148, Folder 11)
      - Germany, Jones, Arthur, "Science and Moral Responsibility," undated (Box 148, Folder 12)
      - Germany, Jones, Arthur, "Liberation of Berlin," undated (Box 148, Folder 13)
      - Germany, Munich, 1963-1964 (Box 148, Folder 14)
      - Germany, Munich, 1965-1966 (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - Germany, Munich, 1965-1966 (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - Germany, Munich- Peterson, Jasper, 1952 (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - Germany, Munich- Peterson, Jasper, 1953 (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - Germany, Munich- Peterson, Jasper, 1953 (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - Germany, Munich- Peterson, Jasper, 1954 (Box 149, Folder 6)
      - Germany, Munich- Peterson, Jasper, 1955 (Box 149, Folder 7)
      - Germany, Miscellaneous Committees-Berlin, 1951-1953 (Box 149, Folder 8)
      - Germany, Miscellaneous Committees- Cause, 1953-1954 (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - Germany, Miscellaneous Committees- Göhingen, 1955 (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - Germany, Miscellaneous Committees- Nacht und Nebel, 1956 (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - Germany, Miscellaneous Committees- Reuter (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence, 1955-1965 (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "A-C," 1966 (Box 150, Folder 6)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence, "D-J," 1966 (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence, "K-R," 1966 (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence, "S-Z," 1966 (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - Gorkin, Julien, 1955-1957 (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - Gorkin, Julien, 1958-1960 (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - Gorkin, Julien, 1961-1963 (Box 151, Folder 6)
      - Gorkin, Julien Reports, 1956-1961 (Box 151, Folder 7)
      - Gorwala, A. D., 1955-1959 (Box 151, Folder 8)
      - Graubard, Stephen, 1964-1965 (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - Graubard, Stephen, 1964-1965 Folder 3: Grauer, Alvin, 1954 (Box 152, Folder 2)
      - Greece, 1950-1954 (Box 152, Folder 4)
      - Greece, "White Paper on Internment Camps in Greece," 1953 (Box 152, Folder 5)
      - Greece- Press clippings, 1954-1956 (Box 152, Folder 6)
      - Greece- Grey, Robert D., 1959 (Box 152, Folder 7)
      - Greece- Griffith, William E., 1960-1966 (Box 152, Folder 8)
      - Greece- Gulbenkian Foundation, 1950-1952 (Box 152, Folder 9)
      - Greece- Gulbenkian Foundation, 1950-1952 (Box 152, Folder 10)
      - Greece- Gulbenkian Foundation, 1953-1955 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Sub-subseries 8: "H"
      - General Correspondence "H," 1956 (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence "H," 1957 (Box 153, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence "H," 1958 (Box 153, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence "H," 1959 (Box 153, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence "H," 1960 (Box 153, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence "H," 1961 (Box 153, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence "H," 1962 (Box 153, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence "H," 1963 (Box 153, Folder 8)
      - General Correspondence "H," 1964 (Box 154, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence "H," 1965-1966 (Box 154, Folder 2)
      - Hamilton, Bernice, 1956 (Box 154, Folder 3)
      - Hamilton, Iain, 1959-1960 (Box 154, Folder 4)
      - Harvard University Library, 1957-1960 (Box 154, Folder 5)
      - Harvard University Press, 1958-1960 (Box 154, Folder 6)
      - Harvard University Russian Research Center, 1957 (Box 154, Folder 7)
      - Hay, Julius, undated (Box 154, Folder 8)
      - Helfritz, Hans, 1962-1963 (Box 154, Folder 9)
      - Hensman, C. R., 1959-1961 (Box 154, Folder 10)
      - Hensman, C. R., 1962-1964 (Box 154, Folder 11)
      - Hinden, Rita, 1955-1957 (Box 154, Folder 12)
      - Hinden, Rita, 1958-1966 (Box 154, Folder 13)
      - Holt, Claire, 1962-1966 (Box 154, Folder 14)
      - Hong Kong, 1959-1962 (Box 154, Folder 15)
      - Hong Kong-Symposium on Economic and Social Problems of the Far East, 1961 (Box 155, Folder 1)
      - Hook, Sidney, 1950-1952 (Box 155, Folder 2)
      - Hook, Sidney, 1953 (Box 155, Folder 3)
      - Hook, Sidney, 1954 (Box 155, Folder 4)
      - Hook, Sidney, 1955 (Box 155, Folder 5)
      - Hook, Sidney, 1956 (Box 155, Folder 6)
      - Hook, Sidney, 1957 (Box 155, Folder 7)
      - Hook, Sidney, 1958-1959 (Box 155, Folder 8)
      - Hook, Sidney, 1960-1967 (Box 155, Folder 9)
      - Hoselitz, Bert, 1956-1957 (Box 155, Folder 10)
      - Hourani, Albert, 1962-1963 (Box 155, Folder 11)
      - Hsu, Yu, 1957-1958 (Box 155, Folder 12)
      - Hubalek, Felix, 1953-1957 (Box 155, Folder 13)
      - Hungary, Anthology of Hungarian Poetry, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 1)
      - Hungary, Confidential Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 156, Folder 2)
      - Hungary, Confidential Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 156, Folder 3)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Gazette [Irodalmi Ujsag], 1957 (Box 156, Folder 4)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Gazette [Irodalmi Ujsag], 1957 (Box 156, Folder 5)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Gazette [Irodalmi Ujsag], 1957 (Box 156, Folder 6)
      - Hungary, Aid to Refugees "A-H," 1957-1958 (Box 156, Folder 7)
      - Hungary, Aid to Refugees "I-R," 1957-1958 (Box 156, Folder 8)
      - Hungary, Aid to Refugees "S-Z," 1957-1958 (Box 156, Folder 9)
      - Hungary, Projects, 1957 (Box 156, Folder 10)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Revolution, 1956-1957 (Box 157, Folder 1)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Revolution, Hungarian Gazette, 1956 (Box 157, Folder 2)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Revolution Protests, 1957-1958 (Box 157, Folder 3)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Revolution, 1957 (Box 157, Folder 4)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Revolution, undated (Box 157, Folder 4a)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Revolution Statements and Articles, 1957-1958 (Box 157, Folder 5)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Revolution Statements and Articles, 1958 (Box 157, Folder 6)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Revolution Statements and Articles, 1957 (Box 157, Folder 7)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Revolution, "Ten Years After," 1966 (Box 157, Folder 8)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Writers Abroad, 1957 (Box 157, Folder 9)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Writers Abroad "A-E," 1958 (Box 157, Folder 10)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Writers Abroad "F-H," 1958 (Box 158, Folder 1)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Writers Abroad "I," 1958 (Box 158, Folder 2)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Writers Abroad "J-R," 1958 (Box 158, Folder 3)
      - Hungary, Hungarian Writers Abroad "S-Z," 1958 (Box 158, Folder 4)